What are you doing?
何やってるんですか?
I'm reading a book at the library.
図書館で本読んでる
Is this the library?
ここ図書館なの?
Library in underwear?
下着で図書館?
It's going to be weird for everyone, isn't it?
変に思われるでしょ、みんなに
In the library...it's a library.
図書館で...図書館ですって
What book are you reading?
何の本読んでる?
Japanese folk tales.
日本昔話
Japanese folktales?
日本昔話?
nice.
いいね
So, let's start telling Japanese folk tales now.
じゃあ今から日本昔話を やっちゃうか
Let's make Japanese folk tales come true.
日本昔話を実現させよう
What do you like about Japanese folk tales?
日本昔話の話って何が好きなの?
Momotaro.
桃太郎
Then I'm the demon.
じゃあ、俺が鬼
article?
記事?
Momotaro.
桃太郎
So, demon.
で、鬼
It's born from peaches.
桃から生まれるじゃん
I'll show you that peach now.
その桃を今からお見せします
I'll show you the peach.
桃をお見せします
A peach has appeared.
桃が出てきました
It's a nice peach.
いい桃してるよ
below
下の
...
I'm shaking, Momo.
震 えてます、桃
Please sit down.
座ってもらって
And then, the body until the peach
そして、 身体を桃まで
with my own hands
自 分の手で
Then I would like to be attacked by Momotaro-chan.
それでは 桃太郎ちゃんに 攻められたいと思います
I can see the weapon
武器が見えるから
A weapon.
武 器が
hey.
ね
Now, please look at the camera.
じゃあ、カメラを 見てください
Looking at the camera, looking at the camera.
カメラを見ながら 目線はカメラ
Would you like me to go further and further down?
どんどん下に行ってもらおうか
Look at the camera too.
カメラも見てね
V zone.
Vゾーン
V.
I.
O.
Can I have a look at your V?
のVを お前見てもらっていいですか?
While doing so.
こちょこちょしながら
V.
I.
O.
V.
のVを
V
V further down.
もっと下のV
It just happens to be the V on the side.
たまたま横のV
Oh yeah, it feels good.
そうそう、おー気持ちいい
Just look at me.
俺だけを見てくれ
Oh, that's it.
おーそこそこ
Finally, please make your dick bigger.
最後に、おちんちんフェラー 大きくしてください
Can I put my penis in Momotaro-chan?
俺の おちんちん 桃太郎ちゃんに入れていい?
With that, you can exterminate demons.
それで 鬼退治ができるよ
Gold bar.
金棒
Can I put a gold bar in it?
金棒入れちゃいます?
Excuse me.
失礼します
feeling?
気持ち?
It's so tiny.
すごいちっちゃい
Maybe I should give you a blow job.
フェラーをしてもらおうかな
Delicious.
う まいね
Even if you go, just stay there.
行ってもそのままでよ
good?
いい?
It was fun.
楽しかったです
See you next week.
また来週